iranianlivetv.eu 2018-12-27

# Watch privacy_policy - Iran TV Series - parsi1hd.com

###        _Watch Live TV and Radio Channels Online_

**Enjoy watching the most popular Iranian and Live TV channels, Music videos and Movies in Farsi, and listen to live radio streams from Iran and all around the world. If there is any channel you miss and would like to watch it here, so tell us and we will provide the stream if possible.**

|   |    
  |    
   
|   
---  
Live TVs  
Frequency List  
TV Series  
Series Page 2  
Useful Links  
Copyright Notice  
Privacy Policy  
|  |    
| Privacy Policy  
---  
  
Iranianlivetv takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.  
Routine Information Collection  
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
Where necessary, iranianlivetv uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.  
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.  
Controlling Your Privacy  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.  
Contact Information  
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to info@iranianlivetv.com for further clarification.  

|   
|   
  |  |   |   |   |   |   |
